{
    "subject": "resource/Fabio_Tinazzi",
    "predicate": "ontology/team",
    "object": "resource/Fermana_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "Fabio Tinazzi is part of the Fermana F.C. team.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9246771335601807,
            "question": "Who is Fabio Tinazzi part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8819348216056824,
            "question": "What team is Fabio Tinazzi on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7976655960083008,
            "question": "Is Fabio Tinazzi a professional athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7933928966522217,
            "question": "Name the football club that Fabio Tinazzi belongs to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7554249167442322,
            "question": "Is Fermana F.C. a local or national team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.726861834526062,
            "question": "What league does Fermana F.C. compete in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6939331293106079,
            "question": "What sport is Fermana F.C. associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.680670440196991,
            "question": "Where is Fermana F.C. based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6765909790992737,
            "question": "What position does Fabio Tinazzi play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6273897886276245,
            "question": "Does Fabio Tinazzi play for a football club?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fabio Tinazzi is part of the Fermana F.C. team.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3365_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position does Fabio Tinazzi play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3365_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Fermana F.C. based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3365_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport is Fermana F.C. associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3365_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3365_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no mention of Fabio Tinazzi being part of the Fermana F.C. team in any of the provided documents. The only mentions of Fabio Tinazzi are related to his connection with Calcio a 7, Memorial Tinazzi, and wine production through the company Tinazzi."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided do not mention any information about Fabio Tinazzi being part of the Fermana F.C. team. The information in the documents relates to soccer, specifically 7-a-side soccer, and detailed stats of a player named Fabio Tinazzi, but there is no mention of his affiliation with any specific football (soccer) club like Fermana F.C."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Fabio Tinazzi is a professional soccer player (as per context information #2, #3, and #4) and a wine producer (context information #6), not a member of the Fermana F.C. team, as there's no mention in any given context about his association with a football club.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context focuses on Fabio Tinazzi's soccer statistics, wine production by a company named Tinazzi, and a Brazilian boxer named F\u00e1bio Souza de Oliveira. There is no mention of Fermana F.C. or any connection between Fabio Tinazzi and the team.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there is no mention of Fermana F.C. in the provided context information, and the player Fabio Tinazzi (later referred to as F\u00e1bio Souza de Oliveira) seems to be associated with a different field (soccer and boxing), not football or a team like Fermana F.C.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Fabio Tinazzi being part of the Fermana F.C. team, nor does it provide any details about his current or past club affiliations. Instead, it refers to a 7-a-side soccer game and detailed stats of Fabio Tinazzi, which are related to his athletic career but do not indicate his affiliation with specific teams beyond these contexts.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}